https://www.womeninfilm.ca/privacy.html

ProgrammingTricksters and Writers
Producer's Panel SeriesProducer's Panel Series Van 2019Producer's Panel Bio's Van 2019
Producer's Panel Series Vic 2019Producer's Panel Bio's Vic 2019
Film Festival2020 Film FestivalVIWFF 2020 Schedule
Screenplay Competition2020 International Screenplay Competition
Privacy Policy
Your privacy is a matter of paramount concern to Women In Film & Television Vancouver (WIFTV) as you visit our website and/or communicate with us via e-mail. We take this opportunity to provide you with explicit information on how we collect, gather, and identify information during your visit to www.womeninfilm.ca.This information may be expanded or updated as we modify or develop the site. It is for this reason that we suggest that you review this policy periodically.Personally identifiable information refers to information that tells us specifically who you are, such as your name, phone number, e-mail or postal address. In most cases, this information is of benefit, or even essential, for us to provide the personalized or enhanced services that you request.  Under no circumstances whatsoever, is any such personal information you may share with WIFTV provided to other individuals, companies or organizations. The extent of personally identifiable information that you choose to disclose to WIFTV is at your discretion. The only way personal information would be made known to WIFTV is if you provide it to us in conjunction with a request for information and/or our services.What information do we collect and how do we use it? WIFTV collects information on our users by your voluntary submissions. We also collect, store and accumulate certain non-personally identifiable information concerning your use of this website, such as: which of our pages and services are of most interest to our clients and prospects.The information WIFTV  collects is used only for internal review; to quantify interest in products and services and improve the content of the site, thus making your user experience more valuable; and to let you know about products and services in which you may be interested.E-mail:  If you have provided us your e-mail address, WIFTV periodically sends promotional communications about services offered. If you do not wish to receive e-mail information fromWIFTV at any time, please advise us of the fact by e-mailing info@womeninfilm.ca. You may also write to us at:Women In Film & Television Vancouver462 - 411 Dunsmuir StreetVancouver, British ColumbiaV6B 1X4
By using our website, you consent only to the collection and use of the information as delineated in this Privacy Policy.We thank you for visiting the WIFTV site.
Announcements
Announcements
Check out WIFTV's Blog
posted on 1:23 PM, July 23, 2014
Did you know you can read about local women working in the industry on the WIFTV blog?
Check it out at: wiftv.wordpress.com
Do you know a woman you'd like to interview for the blog?  Contact communications@womeninfilm.ca....
Women in film & Television Vancouver Site Map | Privacy Policy | Admin Login
Powered by Exware Association Management
